Guide to the Arena Stage records, 1949-2010
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections Research Center.
- Series 2: Production files, 1950-2010 (Boxes 197-588, 654-663)
  - Subseries 2.1: Dramaturgical files, 1958-2010
    - Uncle Vanya - Call Board Staff, Undated (Box 289, Folder 7)
    - Uncle Vanya Research (1 of 6), 1997-1998 (Box 289, Folder 8)
    - Uncle Vanya Research (2 of 6), 1997-1998 (Box 289, Folder 9)
    - Uncle Vanya Research (3 of 6), 1997-1998 (Box 289, Folder 10)
    - Uncle Vanya Research (4 of 6), 1997-1998 (Box 290, Folder 1)
    - Uncle Vanya Research (5 of 6), 1997-1998 (Box 290, Folder 2)
    - Uncle Vanya Research (6 of 6), 1997-1998 (Box 290, Folder 3)
    - 33 Variations Research Packet (1 of 2), 2006 (Box 290, Folder 4)
    - 33 Variations Research Packet (2 of 2), 2006 (Box 290, Folder 5)
    - 33 Variations Research Packet (1 of 2), September 2006 (Box 290, Folder 6)
    - 33 Variations Research Packet (2 of 2), September 2006 (Box 290, Folder 7)
    - 33 Variations Research Packet, 2006-2007 (Box 291, Folder 1)
    - 33 Variations Research Packet (1 of 2), March 2007 (Box 291, Folder 2)
    - 33 Variations Research Packet (2 of 2), March 2007 (Box 291, Folder 3)
    - 33 Variations Research Packet (1 of 2), 2006-2008 (Box 291, Folder 4)
    - 33 Variations Research Packet (2 of 2), 2006-2008 (Box 291, Folder 5)
    - 33 Variations Index (1 of 4), 2007 (Box 292, Folder 1)
    - 33 Variations Index (2 of 4), 2007 (Box 292, Folder 2)
    - 33 Variations Index (3 of 4), 2007 (Box 292, Folder 3)
    - 33 Variations Index (4 of 4), 2007 (Box 292, Folder 4)
    - 33 Variations La Jolla Draft, 2008 (Box 292, Folder 5)
    - 33 Variations Final Script, 2008 (Box 292, Folder 6)
    - The Visit (1 of 6), 1991-1992 (Box 293, Folder 1)
    - The Visit (2 of 6), 1991-1992 (Box 293, Folder 2)
    - The Visit (3 of 6), 1991-1992 (Box 293, Folder 3)
    - The Visit (4 of 6), 1991-1992 (Box 293, Folder 4)
    - The Visit (5 of 6), 1991-1992 (Box 293, Folder 5)
    - The Visit (6 of 6), 1991-1992 (Box 293, Folder 6)
    - Vivisections from the Blown Mind, April 26, 1991 - May 26, 1991 (Box 293, Folder 7)
    - Vivisections from the Blown Mind (1 of 5), 1990-1991 (Box 294, Folder 1)
    - Vivisections from the Blown Mind (2 of 5), 1990-1991 (Box 294, Folder 2)
    - Vivisections from the Blown Mind (3 of 5), 1990-1991 (Box 294, Folder 3)
    - Vivisections from the Blown Mind (4 of 5), 1990-1991 (Box 294, Folder 4)
    - Vivisections from the Blown Mind (5 of 5), 1990-1991 (Box 294, Folder 5)
    - Voices at the Threshold (1 of 4), Undated (Box 294, Folder 6)
    - Voices at the Threshold (2 of 4), Undated (Box 294, Folder 7)
    - Voices at the Threshold (3 of 4), Undated (Box 294, Folder 8)
    - Voices at the Threshold (4 of 4), Undated (Box 295, Folder 1)
    - Voir Dire (1 of 4), 1996-1997 (Box 295, Folder 2)
    - Voir Dire (2 of 4), 1996-1997 (Box 295, Folder 3)
    - Voir Dire (3 of 4), 1996-1997 (Box 295, Folder 4)
    - Voir Dire (4 of 4), 1996-1997 (Box 295, Folder 5)
    - The Waiting Room Research (1 of 2), 1995-1996 (Box 295, Folder 6)
    - The Waiting Room Research (2 of 2), 1995-1996 (Box 295, Folder 7)
    - The Waiting Room Research (1 of 4), 1995-1996 (Box 296, Folder 1)
    - The Waiting Room Research (2 of 4), 1995-1996 (Box 296, Folder 2)
    - The Waiting Room Research (3 of 4), 1995-1996 (Box 296, Folder 3)
    - The Waiting Room Research (4 of 4), 1995-1996 (Box 296, Folder 4)
    - A Walk in the Woods, 1989 (Box 296, Folder 5)
    - The Way of the World "A" Script, 1992-1993 (Box 296, Folder 6)
    - The Way of the World "B" Script, 1992-1993 (Box 296, Folder 7)
    - The Way of the World (1 of 7), 1992-1993 (Box 297, Folder 1)
    - The Way of the World (2 of 7), 1992-1993 (Box 297, Folder 2)
    - The Way of the World (3 of 7), 1992-1993 (Box 297, Folder 3)
    - The Way of the World (4 of 7), 1992-1993 (Box 297, Folder 4)
    - The Way of the World (5 of 7), 1992-1993 (Box 297, Folder 5)
    - The Way of the World (6 of 7), 1992-1993 (Box 297, Folder 6)
    - The Way of the World (7 of 7), 1992-1993 (Box 297, Folder 7)
    - The Way of the World - Notes and Queries, 1992-1993 (Box 298, Folder 1)
    - The Way of the World - Script, 1992-1993 (Box 298, Folder 2)
    - The Way of the World - Research (1 of 2), 1992-1993 (Box 298, Folder 3)
    - The Way of the World - Research (2 of 2), 1992-1993 (Box 298, Folder 4)
    - The Way of the World - Sir Geoffrey Kheller, 1992-1993 (Box 298, Folder 5)
    - The Way of the World - The First English Actress, 1992-1993 (Box 298, Folder 6)
    - The Way of the World - A Biographical Dictionary, 1992-1993 (Box 298, Folder 7)
    - The Way of the World - The Pageant of Stuart England, 1992-1993 (Box 298, Folder 8)
    - The Way of the World - Three Family Formation, 1992-1993 (Box 298, Folder 9)
    - The Way of the World - Analysis Essay, 1992-1993 (Box 298, Folder 10)
    - The Way of the World - James Boswell and His World, 1992-1993 (Box 298, Folder 11)
    - The Way of the World - Reviews, 1992-1993 (Box 298, Folder 12)
    - The Way of the World - Marriage System in England, 1992-1993 (Box 298, Folder 13)
    - The Way of the World - English Social History, 1992-1993 (Box 298, Folder 14)
    - The Way of the World - The Court Willis of the Restoration, 1992-1993 (Box 298, Folder 15)
    - The Way of the World - Time Period Research, 1992-1993 (Box 298, Folder 16)
    - The Way of the World - Research Notes, 1992-1993 (Box 298, Folder 17)
    - The Way of the World - John Dryden and His World, 1992-1993 (Box 298, Folder 18)
    - Well Research Packet (1 of 3), 2007 (Box 299, Folder 1)
    - Well Research Packet (2 of 3), 2007 (Box 299, Folder 2)
    - Well Research Packet (3 of 3), 2007 (Box 299, Folder 3)
    - What the Butler Saw (1 of 3), Undated (Box 299, Folder 1)
    - What the Butler Saw (2 of 3), Undated (Box 299, Folder 2)
    - What the Butler Saw (3 of 3), Undated (Box 299, Folder 3)
    - The Women - 1939 Film Script (1 of 6), 1998 (Box 300, Folder 1)
    - The Women (2 of 6), 1998 (Box 300, Folder 2)
    - The Women (3 of 6), 1998 (Box 300, Folder 3)
    - The Women (4 of 6), 1998 (Box 300, Folder 4)
    - The Women (5 of 6), 1998 (Box 300, Folder 5)
    - The Women (6 of 6), 1998 (Box 300, Folder 6)
    - The Women of Brewster Place (1 of 2), 2007 (Box 300, Folder 7)
    - The Women of Brewster Place (2 of 2), 2007 (Box 300, Folder 8)
    - The Women of Brewster Place Research Packet (1 of 2), Summer 2007 (Box 301, Folder 1)
    - The Women of Brewster Place Research Packet (2 of 2), Summer 2007 (Box 301, Folder 2)
    - A Wonderful Life- Script #1 Draft, 1985 (Box 301, Folder 3)
    - A Wonderful Life- Script #2, 1990 (Box 301, Folder 4)
    - A Wonderful Life- Script #3, 1991 (Box 301, Folder 5)
    - A Wonderful Life- Script #4, 1991 (Box 301, Folder 6)
    - A Wonderful Life - Correspondence and Related Articles, 1990-1991 (Box 302, Folder 1)
    - A Wonderful Life - Horn Sheet Music (1 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 302, Folder 2)
    - A Wonderful Life - Horn Sheet Music (2 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 302, Folder 3)
    - A Wonderful Life - Production Materials, 1991 (Box 302, Folder 4)
    - A Wonderful Life - Reed 2 Sheet Music (1 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 302, Folder 5)
    - A Wonderful Life - Reed 2 Sheet Music (2 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 302, Folder 6)
    - A Wonderful Life - Reed 3 Sheet Music (1 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 302, Folder 7)
    - A Wonderful Life - Reed 3 Sheet Music (2 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 302, Folder 8)
    - A Wonderful Life - Set Design Sketches, Undated (Box 302, Folder 9)
    - A Wonderful Life - Percussion Sheet Music (1 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 303, Folder 1)
    - A Wonderful Life - Percussion Sheet Music (2 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 303, Folder 2)
    - A Wonderful Life - Percussion Sheet Music Extras (1 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 303, Folder 3)
    - A Wonderful Life - Percussion Sheet Music Extras (2 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 303, Folder 4)
    - A Wonderful Life - Trumpet 1 Sheet Music (1 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 303, Folder 5)
    - A Wonderful Life - Trumpet 1 Sheet Music (2 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 303, Folder 6)
    - A Wonderful Life - Reed 1 Sheet Music (1 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 303, Folder 7)
    - A Wonderful Life - Reed 1 Sheet Music (2 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 303, Folder 8)
    - A Wonderful Life - Piano Sheet Music, 1991-1992 (Box 304, Folder 1)
    - A Wonderful Life - Synthesizer Sheet Music (1 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 304, Folder 2)
    - A Wonderful Life - Synthesizer Sheet Music (2 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 304, Folder 3)
    - A Wonderful Life - Trombone Sheet Music (1 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 304, Folder 4)
    - A Wonderful Life - Trombone Sheet Music (2 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 304, Folder 5)
    - A Wonderful Life - Trumpet 2 Sheet Music (1 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 304, Folder 6)
    - A Wonderful Life - Trumpet 2 Sheet Music (2 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 304, Folder 7)
    - A Wonderful Life - Bass Sheet Music (1 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 305, Folder 1)
    - A Wonderful Life - Bass Sheet Music (2 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 305, Folder 2)
    - A Wonderful Life - Conductor Sheet Music (1 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 305, Folder 3)
    - A Wonderful Life - Conductor Sheet Music (2 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 305, Folder 4)
    - A Wonderful Life - Keyboard 2 Sheet Music (1 of 3), 1991-1992 (Box 305, Folder 5)
    - A Wonderful Life - Keyboard 2 Sheet Music (2 of 3), 1991-1992 (Box 305, Folder 6)
    - A Wonderful Life - Keyboard 2 Sheet Music (3 of 3), 1991-1992 (Box 305, Folder 7)
    - A Wonderful Life - Cello (1 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 306, Folder 1)
    - A Wonderful Life - Cello (2 of 2), 1991-1992 (Box 306, Folder 2)
    - Yellowman, 2003-2004 (Box 306, Folder 3)
    - Yerma - Scripts and Research Materials, 1991 (Box 306, Folder 4)
    - Yerma - Images (1 of 2), 1991 (Box 306, Folder 5)
    - Yerma - Images (2 of 2), 1991 (Box 306, Folder 6)
    - Yerma - Production and Research Materials, 1991 (Box 306, Folder 7)
    - You Can't Take it With You - Script and Production Guides, 1997-1998 (Box 307, Folder 1)
    - You Can't Take it With You - Notes and Clippings (1 of 2), 1997-1998 (Box 307, Folder 2)
    - You Can't Take it With You - Notes and Clippings (2 of 2), 1997-1998 (Box 307, Folder 3)
  - Subseries 2.2: Playwright subject files, 1953-1995
    This subseries contains research on various playwrights, both living and dead, whose work has been performed at Arena.
    - George Abbott photo, undated (Box 308, Folder 1)
    - Edward Albee, 1969-1974 (Box 308, Folder 2)
    - Robert Anderson, 1970 (Box 308, Folder 3)
    - Jean Anouilh, 1969-1988 (Box 308, Folder 4)
    - Sholem Ansky, 1974 (Box 308, Folder 5)
    - Alan Ayckbourn, 1975-1988 (Box 308, Folder 6)
    - Restoration - Edward Bond, 1962-1988 (Box 308, Folder 7)
    - Anna Marie Barlow, late 1960s (Box 308, Folder 8)
    - Samuel Beckett, 1986 (Box 308, Folder 9)
    - Brendan Behan, circa 1975 (Box 308, Folder 10)
    - Michael Brady, 1984 (Box 308, Folder 11)
    - Daniel Berrigan, 1972 (Box 308, Folder 12)
    - Bertolt Brecht (1 of 2), 1970-1983 (Box 308, Folder 13)
    - Bertolt Brecht (2 of 2), 1969-1985 (Box 308, Folder 14)
    - Robert Brittan (playwright/composer), 1995 (Box 308, Folder 15)
    - John Mason Brown, 1969 (Box 308, Folder 16)
    - Alexander Buzo, 1972 (Box 308, Folder 17)
    - Truman Capote, 1971 (Box 308, Folder 18)
    - Paddy Chayefsky, 1969 (Box 308, Folder 19)
    - Anton Chekhov (1 of 3), circa 1970s-1980s (Box 308, Folder 20)
    - Anton Chekhov (2 of 3), circa 1970s-1980s (Box 308, Folder 21)
    - Anton Chekhov (3 of 3), 1970-1986 (Box 308, Folder 22)
    - Agatha Christie, 1975-1976 (Box 309, Folder 1)
    - Caryl Churchill, 1984 (Box 309, Folder 2)
    - Noel Coward, 1970-1975 (Box 309, Folder 3)
    - Mart Crowley, late 1960s (Box 309, Folder 4)
    - Neil Cuthbert, 1975 (Box 309, Folder 5)
    - DC area playwrights, undated (Box 309, Folder 6)
    - Dostoevski, 1969 (Box 309, Folder 7)
    - Christopher Durang, 1977-1985 (Box 309, Folder 8)
    - Friedrich Durrenmatt, 1971 (Box 309, Folder 9)
    - Sherman Edwards, 1970 (Box 309, Folder 10)
    - Lone Elder, 1970-1971 (Box 309, Folder 11)
    - T.S. Elliott, 1969 (Box 309, Folder 12)
    - Jules Feiffer, 1970-1971 (Box 309, Folder 13)
    - Jules Feiffer and Georges Feydeau, 1969-1974 (Box 309, Folder 14)
    - Foreigners: visitors and playwrights, 1982-1986 (Box 309, Folder 15)
    - Michael Frayan, 1984 (Box 309, Folder 16)
    - Max Frisch, 1967-1975 (Box 309, Folder 17)
    - Athol Fugard (1 of 3), 1975-1986 (Box 309, Folder 18)
    - Athol Fugard (2 of 3), 1981 (Box 309, Folder 19)
    - Athol Fugard (3 of 3), 1967-1982 (Box 309, Folder 20)
    - Robert Ganshaw, 1970 (Box 309, Folder 21)
    - Herb Gardner, 1970 (Box 309, Folder 22)
    - Anthony Giardina, 1977-1978 (Box 309, Folder 23)
    - Anthony Giardina, 1985-1994 (Box 309, Folder 24)
    - Jean Genet, 1976 (Box 309, Folder 25)
    - William Gibson, 1970-1972 (Box 309, Folder 26)
    - William Gillette, 1974-1975 (Box 309, Folder 27)
    - Janusz Glowacki, 1989 (Box 310, Folder 1)
    - Carlo Goldoni, 1974-1975 (Box 310, Folder 2)
    - Charles Gordone, 1968-1970 (Box 310, Folder 3)
    - Maxim Gorky, 1976 (Box 310, Folder 4)
    - Simon Gray, 1977-1991 (Box 310, Folder 5)
    - Stanley R. Greenberg, 1970-1971 (Box 310, Folder 6)
    - Jerzy Grotowski (Polish innovative theatre director and theorist), 1969-1970 (Box 310, Folder 7)
    - John Guare, 1984-1986 (Box 310, Folder 8)
    - A.R. Gurney, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 310, Folder 9)
    - Gunter Grass (German playwright), 1965-1972 (Box 310, Folder 10)
    - William Hanley, 1968-1970 (Box 310, Folder 11)
    - Lorraine Hansberry, 1964-1971 (Box 310, Folder 12)
    - Moss Hart, 1974 (Box 310, Folder 13)
    - Father Hartke, 1984 (Box 310, Folder 14)
    - Hecht and MacArthur, 1974-1975 (Box 310, Folder 15)
    - Lillian Hellman, 1961-1976 (Box 310, Folder 16)
    - Beth Henly, 1984 (Box 310, Folder 17)
    - Albert Hirschfeld, undated (Box 310, Folder 18)
    - Israel Horowitz, 1969-1976 (Box 310, Folder 19)
    - Odon von Horvath (Box 310, Folder 20)
    - Henrik Ibsen, 1969-1986 (Box 311, Folder 1)
    - Eugene Ionesco, 1965-1971 (Box 311, Folder 2)
    - Julie Jenson, 1986 (Box 311, Folder 3)
    - Preston Jones, 1979 (Box 311, Folder 4)
    - Sidney Kingsly, 1973 (Box 311, Folder 5)
    - John Kneubuhl, 1973-1974 (Box 311, Folder 6)
    - Xaver Franz Kroetz, 1984 (Box 311, Folder 7)
    - Eugene Labiche, 1986 (Box 311, Folder 8)
    - Shirley Lauro, 1984 (Box 311, Folder 9)
    - Lawrence and Lee, 1970 (Box 311, Folder 10)
    - Jerome Lawrence and Robert E. Lee, The Night Thoreau Spent in Jail, 1970 (Box 311, Folder 11)
    - David Mamet, 1975-1986 (Box 311, Folder 12)
    - Edgar Lee Masters, 1970-1975 (Box 311, Folder 13)
    - McNally, Terrence, Undated (Box 311, Folder 14)
    - Patrick Meyers, circa 1980s (Box 311, Folder 15)
    - Patrick Meyers, 1984 (Box 311, Folder 16)
    - Midwest Playwrights Program, 1982-1983 (Box 311, Folder 17)
    - Moliere, 1969-1984 (Box 311, Folder 18)
    - Edmoore, 1975 (Box 311, Folder 19)
    - Tad Mosel, circa 1970s (Box 311, Folder 20)
    - Slawomir Mrozek, 1969-1979 (Box 311, Folder 21)
    - Peter Nichols, 1975-1984 (Box 311, Folder 22)
    - Marsha Norman, 1984-1986 (Box 311, Folder 23)
    - Clifford Odets, 1963-1984 (Box 312, Folder 1)
    - Eugene O'Neill, 1953-1976 (Box 312, Folder 2)
    - Istvan Orkeny, 1982-1987 (Box 312, Folder 3)
    - Istvan Orkeny, circa 1980s (Box 312, Folder 4)
    - Joe Orton, 1970 (Box 312, Folder 5)
    - Paul Osborne, 1973 (Box 312, Folder 6)
    - Louise Page, 1982-1984 (Box 312, Folder 7)
    - Luigi Pirandello, 1963-1988 (Box 312, Folder 8)
    - Harold Pinter, 1965-1984 (Box 312, Folder 9)
    - Sylvia Plath, 1974 (Box 312, Folder 10)
    - David Rabe, 1984 (Box 312, Folder 11)
    - Jonathan Reynolds, 1983 (Box 312, Folder 12)
    - Ronald Ribman, 1980 (Box 312, Folder 13)
    - Sandberg, Carl, 1970 (Box 312, Folder 14)
    - Jean-Paul Sartre, circa 1980s (Box 312, Folder 15)
    - Arthur Schnitzler, 1985 (Box 313, Folder 1)
    - Peter Shaffer, 1977 (Box 313, Folder 2)
    - George Bernard Shaw, 1970-1995 (Box 313, Folder 3)
    - Sam Shepard, 1970-1988 (Box 313, Folder 4)
    - Paul Sills, 1971 (Box 313, Folder 5)
    - Neil Simon, 1969-1973 (Box 313, Folder 6)
    - Mayo Simons, 1984 (Box 313, Folder 7)
    - Solzhenitsyn, 1970-1974 (Box 313, Folder 8)
    - William Soroyan, circa 1970s (Box 313, Folder 9)
    - Stage Four playwrights, 1989-1990 (Box 313, Folder 10)
    - Stallings and Anderson, circa 1970s (Box 313, Folder 11)
    - John Steinbeck, 1970s (Box 313, Folder 12)
    - Tom Stoppard, 1973-1987 (Box 313, Folder 13)
    - David Storey, circa 1970s-1980s (Box 313, Folder 14)
    - August Strindberg, 1966 (Box 313, Folder 15)
    - Brandon Thomas, 1970 (Box 314, Folder 1)
    - Dylan Thomas, early 1970s (Box 314, Folder 2)
    - Peter Ustinov, 1984 (Box 314, Folder 3)
    - Kurt Vonnegut, Jr., 1974 (Box 314, Folder 4)
    - Derek Walcott, 1978-1979 (Box 314, Folder 5)
    - Wendy Wasserstein, 1984-1986 (Box 314, Folder 6)
    - Michael Weller, 1979-1986 (Box 314, Folder 7)
    - Norman Wexler, 1970s (Box 314, Folder 8)
    - E.A. Whitehead, 1974 (Box 314, Folder 9)
    - Ron Whyte, 1973-1981 (Box 314, Folder 10)
    - Oscar Wilde, 1973-1980s (Box 314, Folder 11)
    - Thornton Wilder, 1962-1975 (Box 314, Folder 12)
    - Tennessee Williams, 1969-1976 (Box 314, Folder 13)
    - August Wilson, 1984-1988 (Box 314, Folder 14)
    - Lanford Wilson, 1973-1975 (Box 314, Folder 15)
    - Virginia Woolf - Edna O'Brien, 1985 (Box 314, Folder 16)
  - Subseries 2.3: Production files, 1950-2001
    This subseries includes scripts, blocking information, correspondence, and other material related to the production of Arena's plays.
    - Abyssinia (1 of 4), 1988 (Box 315, Folder 1)
    - Abyssinia (2 of 4), 1988 (Box 315, Folder 2)
    - Abyssinia (3 of 4), 1988 (Box 315, Folder 3)
    - Abyssinia (4 of 4), 1988 (Box 315, Folder 4)
    - The Accidental Death of an Anarchist (1 of 3), 1984 (Box 315, Folder 5)
    - The Accidental Death of an Anarchist (2 of 3), 1984 (Box 315, Folder 6)
    - The Accidental Death of an Anarchist (3 of 3), 1984 (Box 315, Folder 7)
    - The Adding Machine (1 of 2), 1951 (Box 316, Folder 1)
    - The Adding Machine (2 of 2), 1951 (Box 316, Folder 2)
    - The Affair (1 of 2), 1963-1964 (Box 316, Folder 3)
    - The Affair (2 of 2), 1963-1964 (Box 316, Folder 4)
    - African Company - R3, 1992-1993 (Box 316, Folder 5)
    - African Company - Blood Knot production book (1 of 2), 1993 (Box 316, Folder 6)
    - African Company - Blood Knot production book (2 of 2), 1993 (Box 316, Folder 7)
    - The African Company presents Richard III, 1992-1993 (Box 316, Folder 8)
    - After the Fall - Hong Kong (1 of 2), 1979 (Box 316, Folder 9)
    - After the Fall - Hong Kong (2 of 2), 1979 (Box 316, Folder 10)
    - After the Fall, 1980 (Box 317, Folder 1)
    - After the Fall, 1981 (Box 317, Folder 2)
    - After the Fall - Hong Kong (1 of 3), 1980 (Box 317, Folder 3)
    - After the Fall - Hong Kong (2 of 3), 1980 (Box 317, Folder 4)
    - After the Fall - Hong Kong (3 of 3), 1980 (Box 317, Folder 5)
    - After the Fall - Arena, 1979-1980 (Box 317, Folder 6)
    - Ah, Wilderness! (1 of 3), 1978-1979 (Box 318, Folder 1)
    - Ah, Wilderness! (2 of 3), 1978-1979 (Box 318, Folder 2)
    - Ah, Wilderness! (3 of 3), 1978-1979 (Box 318, Folder 3)
    - Alexis, We Love You - Recycled, Circa 1970s (Box 318, Folder 4)
    - Alice in Wonderland (1 of 2), 1950-1951 (Box 318, Folder 5)
    - Alice in Wonderland (2 of 2), 1950-1951 (Box 318, Folder 6)
    - Almost Blue - production notes, January 1995 (Box 318, Folder 7)
    - Almost Blue - prompt script, 1994-1995 (Box 318, Folder 8)
    - All American Repertory, 1975 (Box 318, Folder 9)
    - All My Sons - rehearsal/performance notes, 1999-2000 (Box 318, Folder 10)
    - All My Sons - Daily Stage Manager's Report/Program, 1999-2000 (Box 318, Folder 11)
    - All My Sons - paperwork, 1999-2000 (Box 318, Folder 12)
    - All My Sons - calling script, 1999-2000 (Box 318, Folder 13)
    - All My Sons - blocking script, 1999-2000 (Box 319, Folder 1)
    - All The King's Men (1 of 7), 1987-1988 (Box 319, Folder 2)
    - All The King's Men (2 of 7), 1987-1988 (Box 319, Folder 3)
    - All The King's Men (3 of 7), 1987-1988 (Box 319, Folder 4)
    - All The King's Men (4 of 7), 1987-1988 (Box 319, Folder 5)
    - All The King's Men (5 of 7), 1987-1988 (Box 319, Folder 6)
    - All The King's Men (6 of 7), 1987-1988 (Box 319, Folder 7)
    - All The King's Men (7 of 7), 1987-1988 (Box 320, Folder 1)
    - All the Way Home (1 of 2), 1963 (Box 320, Folder 2)
    - All the Way Home (2 of 2), 1963 (Box 320, Folder 3)
    - American Buffalo (1 of 2), 1981 (Box 320, Folder 4)
    - American Buffalo (2 of 2), 1981 (Box 320, Folder 5)
    - The American Dream, 1959-1960 (Box 320, Folder 6)
    - The American Play/production book, Playquest (1 of 2), 1992 (Box 321, Folder 1)
    - The American Play/production book, Playquest (2 of 2), 1992 (Box 321, Folder 2)
    - America Play, 1993 (Box 321, Folder 3)
    - American Splendor (1 of 4), 1987-1988 (Box 321, Folder 4)
    - American Splendor (2 of 4), 1987-1988 (Box 321, Folder 5)
    - American Splendor (3 of 4), 1987-1988 (Box 321, Folder 6)
    - American Splendor (4 of 4), 1987-1988 (Box 321, Folder 7)
    - An American Tragedy (1 of 7), 1979-1980 (Box 322, Folder 1)
    - An American Tragedy (2 of 7), 1979-1980 (Box 322, Folder 2)
    - An American Tragedy (3 of 7), 1979-1980 (Box 322, Folder 3)
    - An American Tragedy (4 of 7), 1979-1980 (Box 322, Folder 4)
    - An American Tragedy (5 of 7), 1979-1980 (Box 323, Folder 1)
    - An American Tragedy (6 of 7), 1979-1980 (Box 323, Folder 2)
    - An American Tragedy (7 of 7), 1979-1980 (Box 323, Folder 3)
    - Anarchist safety and accident reports, 1984 (Box 323, Folder 4)
    - Anarchist rehearsal schedule, 1984 (Box 323, Folder 5)
    - Anarchist preliminary plots, 1984 (Box 323, Folder 6)
    - The Andersonville Trial (1 of 3), 1966-1967 (Box 323, Folder 7)
    - The Andersonville Trial (2 of 3), 1966-1967 (Box 323, Folder 8)
    - The Andersonville Trial (3 of 3), 1966-1967 (Box 323, Folder 9)
    - Animal Crackers contact sheets/program, 1998-1999 (Box 323, Folder 10)
    - Animal Crackers schedule, 1998-1999 (Box 323, Folder 11)
    - Animal Crackers rehearsal notes, 1998-1999 (Box 323, Folder 12)
    - Animal Crackers run sheets, 1998-1999 (Box 323, Folder 13)
    - Animal Crackers - 1998/1999 Season - Props (Box 324, Folder 1)
    - Animal Crackers - 1998/1999 Season - Costumes (Box 324, Folder 2)
    - Animal Crackers - 1998/1999 Season - Set/LX/Sound (Box 324, Folder 3)
    - Animal Crackers - 1998/1999 Season - Memos (Box 324, Folder 4)
    - Animal Crackers - 1998/1999 Season - Performance Report (Box 324, Folder 5)
    - Animal Crackers - 1998/1999 Season - Accident Reports (Box 324, Folder 6)
    - Animal Crackers - 1998/1999 Season - Review (Box 324, Folder 7)
    - Animal Crackers - 1998/1999 Season - Blocking Script (Box 324, Folder 8)
    - Animal Crackers - 1998/1999 Season - Choreography Book (1 of 2) (Box 324, Folder 9)
    - Animal Crackers - 1998/1999 Season - Choreography Book (2 of 2) (Box 324, Folder 10)
    - Animal Crackers - Musical Numbers - 1999 Version (1 of 2) (Box 325, Folder 1)
    - Animal Crackers - Musical Numbers - 1999 Version (2 of 2) (Box 325, Folder 2)
    - Animal Crackers - 1998/1999 Season - Score (1 of 2) (Box 325, Folder 3)
    - Animal Crackers - 1998/1999 Season - Score (2 of 2) (Box 325, Folder 4)
    - Animal Crackers - Script, Revised, December 28, 1998 (Box 325, Folder 5)
    - Animal Crackers - Script, Revised, February 19, 1999 (Box 326, Folder 1)